FLAVIEN CHAMAY | IT JUNIOR ENGINEER

Hi, I'm a Tech and Math enthusiast who lived in Canada and Europe and have therefore experienced two different work worlds. I speak/write French and English, have 2 years of professional experience at Capgemini France and personal experience in Python and Django. I did a training on DevOps for 3 months to become an Analyst for Capgemini France.



CONTACT

flavien.chamay@protonmail.com

▼ Toulouse, France

github.com/flavienChamay

IT SKILLS

Programming Languages

Python

c

Java

OCaml

SQL

Bash

LaTeX

Operating Systems

Linux Manjaro | Ubuntu Linux Debian | RHEL

Windows 10



GitHub/Git

Emacs

Vim

Technologies

Django

PostgreSQL

Blockchain

Docker



English B2 grade

Native French

CERTIFICATES & RECOMMENDATIONS

Recommendation Letter from Becton and Dickinson

INTERESTS

A.I., Extraterrestrial life, Mathematical logic, Hacking.

▼ PROJECTS

- Web Blog (Django, Heroku, Personal project in progress).
- Simple Blockchain (Python, Personal project finished): coding of the proof of work, the wallet and data encryption.
- Tic-Tac-Toe Game (Python, Personal project in progress): Minimax algorithm for computer player, CLI interface, save/load mechanisms.
- Planning by satisfiability of logical formulas (Touist, Internship(3 months)): coding, modeling and benchmarking of logic problem solving A.I..
- NeoCampus, real-time sensors (Java, Academic project): GUI coding and data retrieval.
- Caesar encryption (C, Academic project): encryption/decryption of text files.

WORK HISTORY

2017 - 2020

• Auterive & Toulouse, France

m April 2011 - August 2011

Staples
 Quebec, Canada

February 2008 - June 2010

₱ Becton, Dickinson and Company Quebec, Canada Tutor for private lessons in Maths and C.S.

Computer Repairman & IT Consultant

Packaging Operator

EDUCATION

iuly 2021 - september 2021

2017 - 2020

 Paul Sabatier University Toulouse, France

2011 - 2016

Paul Sabatier University Toulouse, France DevOps & Networks Consultant

Computer Science Bachelor Degree

1st & 2nd cycle in Physics 2nd cycle in Maths

GENERAL SKILLS

Model/specify/integrate/maintain/develop an app

Assess client's need

Analyse origin of malfunction

Optimize algo in time/space complexity

Identify/protect confidential data

Understand/write doc. in Eng/Fr

♣ HOBBIES & OCCUPATIONS

